If you're a seller using a North America unified account, you can sell on Amazon.
com,
our U.
S.
website, Amazon.
ca, our Canada website, and Amazon.
com.
MX, our Mexico website with
a single selling account, putting your products in front of millions of customers across North
America.
In this video we'll walk you through creating listings for Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX.
You'll notice through your unified account that your current listings for Amazon.
com
are not automatically created on Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX.
You'll need to add your listings to these sites just like you did when you first listed
them on Amazon.
com.
To make listing creation across multiple sites easier, you can use the Build International
Listings tool.
If the asins you sell on Amazon.
com already exist on Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX, this will
make creating international offers simple.
Be aware that just because a product was created on Amazon.
com does not mean it is automatically
created on our Canada or Mexico websites.
With the Build International Listings tool, you can easily create international offers,
continuously growing your global catalog as more of your listings become available in
Canada or Mexico.
You can modify your pricing strategy to benefit from a currency exchange rate sync and benefit
from a shared inventory pool between marketplaces for SKUs you can fulfill yourself.
We do not currently support connecting fulfillment by Amazon inventory across marketplaces.
You can, however, list FBA inventory separately in Amazon.
com, Amazon.
ca, and Amazon.
com.
MX
selling accounts.
When expanding offers to Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX, you can customize your own pricing strategy.
All offers will be converted to local currency at the time of creation.
Canada listings will be posted in Canadian dollars and Mexico listings in Mexico pesos.
First, you'll need to pick the U.
S.
as your source marketplace for inventory and offers.
The Build International Listing Tool will use your existing offer pricing to place offers
in Canada or Mexico.
You'll have four options for pricing those listings.
The same price as your source marketplace, a percentage above the source marketplace price,
a percentage below the source marketplace price, or a fixed amount above the source marketplace
price.
Remember, currency conversion is already factored in, so these options are for additional price
changes.
Click Save All to apply your changes.
Amazon does not require price parity or equal pricing on its platforms in North America,
so you do not have to price the same way for Amazon.
com as you do for Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX.
Once you've connected your listings, your merchant fulfilled listings will be using a
global SKU.
That means the SKU will be the same across multiple marketplaces and therefore benefit
from a shared inventory pool and lead times to ship.
As an example, let's say one of your lamps is using a global SKU and it sells on Amazon.
ca.
That quantity purchased will be deducted from your Amazon.
ca account as well as everywhere
else you're using the global SKU, like Amazon.
com or Amazon.
com.
MX.
So if you've had eight units of this item and one sold, seven would now be available on
each marketplace within your Seller central account.
The global SKU feature is only available for listings you fulfill yourself.
If you're using fulfillment by Amazon, you'll need to manage your inventory quantities separately
across each website and customize the SKU used for that ASIN in each marketplace.
An easy solution is to add a dash CA or a dash MX to your existing SKU before uploading
it to Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX.
The Build International Listings Tool can help you expand into Canada or Mexico, but
always remember to check with customs, your shipping carrier, and our Amazon policies for
each country to ensure that every offer your listing complies with all applicable laws and
regulations in that country.
To exclude certain SKUs from being connected, simply click on exclude SKUs and list the
SKUs you don't want to sell in Canada or Mexico.
If you have listings you'd like to sell that do not yet exist on Amazon.
ca or Amazon.
com.
MX
sites, you can easily add them using add product one by one or flat file uploads.
You can use these same methods to list any FBA products with a unique SKU.
Note that using an inventory loader file will not work for adding ASINs that are not yet
present on the .
ca or .
com.
MX sites.
For more information, search "North America Unified Account in Seller Central."